{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": "69bc1fd7-eb23-440d-8f25-fa2d092b8aa9",
      "name": "GermanyðŸ‡©ðŸ‡ª"
    },
    {
      "id": "00b522de-ba08-48c6-abb1-51ed4ac997c3",
      "name": "ItalyðŸ‡®ðŸ‡¹"
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "d7e951d9-4476-4fb3-b738-40e7be1064bc",
      "question": "President",
      "answer": "Chief of the state of Germany handling matters of country.",
      "owner": "69bc1fd7-eb23-440d-8f25-fa2d092b8aa9"
    },
    {
      "id": "537a7ab9-4b65-4eb9-b8a0-68d4016d868a",
      "question": "Der Bundestag",
      "answer": "The legislative branch of Germany",
      "owner": "69bc1fd7-eb23-440d-8f25-fa2d092b8aa9"
    },
    {
      "id": "20dd9334-9402-488c-b6e3-ae63937a715c",
      "question": "Albert Einstein",
      "answer": "Physicist born in Germany who formulated the special theory of relativity and the general theory of relativity",
      "owner": "69bc1fd7-eb23-440d-8f25-fa2d092b8aa9"
    },
    {
      "id": "48da6058-4caa-4659-ae42-cb9f06a99b18",
      "question": "Karl Benz",
      "answer": "1886, German who received a patent for the first automobile with three wheels",
      "owner": "69bc1fd7-eb23-440d-8f25-fa2d092b8aa9"
    },
    {
      "id": "b73091df-73f3-4d45-9d7b-f53db39b80c9",
      "question": "Ancienct Rome",
      "answer": "Built around 700 BC",
      "owner": "00b522de-ba08-48c6-abb1-51ed4ac997c3"
    },
    {
      "id": "602bb60d-2a75-4205-a0e3-d6c417cdef60",
      "question": "Collapse of Roman Empire",
      "answer": "400 AD",
      "owner": "00b522de-ba08-48c6-abb1-51ed4ac997c3"
    },
    {
      "id": "d8ddec02-c823-4500-b430-7b7b3971fe94",
      "question": "Years of the Renaissance",
      "answer": "1350-1500 AD",
      "owner": "00b522de-ba08-48c6-abb1-51ed4ac997c3"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9438418-ede4-4bcb-a74d-00530974576f",
      "question": "Effects of a unified Italy",
      "answer": "Rise in nationalism, patriotism, and pride in country",
      "owner": "00b522de-ba08-48c6-abb1-51ed4ac997c3"
    },
    {
      "id": "88c36e40-9b0a-4cd0-888f-52fee0e405da",
      "question": "The Pope or the head of the Roman Catholic Church lives here",
      "answer": "The Vatican, an independent state in Rome",
      "owner": "00b522de-ba08-48c6-abb1-51ed4ac997c3"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f00c36a-c0f0-4e62-9ae3-cd0f3b9fe2ea",
      "question": "dgsgrf",
      "answer": "dgsgrf",
      "owner": "69bc1fd7-eb23-440d-8f25-fa2d092b8aa9"
    },
    {
      "id": "1e15fb88-afda-4839-82f2-026b901b9eb3",
      "question": "kljfg",
      "answer": "dgsgrf",
      "owner": "69bc1fd7-eb23-440d-8f25-fa2d092b8aa9"
    }
  ]
}